<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DJob</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Job</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Pramudia Fitrian Alvarisqi</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_language">Language</string>
    <string name="id">Indonesian</string>
    <string name="en">English</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>

    <string name="joby1">..Pekerjaan Pak Random..</string>
    <string name="joby2">Pak Random adalah seorang Game Developer</string>
    <string name="joby3">Pak Random bergelut di dalam pengembangan Indie Game pertamanya.</string>
    <string name="joby4">Pak Random berencana mengembangkan game nya dalam tenggat waktu 1 tahun.</string>
    <string name="joby5">Pak Random mengalami banyak kesulitan dalam proses pengembangannya.</string>
    <string name="joby6">Pak Random mencari tau ke berbagai platform dan senior dalam pengembangan game.</string>
    <string name="joby7">Pak Random sadar kalau membuat game ternyata tidak semudah itu.</string>
    <string name="joby8">Pak Random dapat mengatasi masalahnya 1 per 1.</string>
    <string name="joby9">Pak Random mulai berhasil menjaga kestabilan proses pengembangan game nya.</string>
    <string name="joby10">Pak Random berhasil merilis game buatannya dalam tenggat waktu yang ditentukan.</string>

    <string name="nama1">Craftsman</string>
    <string name="nama2">Agriculturist</string>
    <string name="nama3">Doctor</string>
    <string name="nama4">Employee</string>
    <string name="nama5">Teacher</string>
    <string name="nama6">Librarian</string>
    <string name="nama7">Fisherman</string>
    <string name="nama8">Tailor</string>
    <string name="nama9">Farmer</string>
    <string name="nama10">Soldier</string>

    <string name="desc1">A person who works in the field of crafts can produce goods. Examples of handicraft products are jewelry, carvings, pottery, woven fabrics, to souvenirs.</string>
    <string name="desc2">Agriculturist is a type of work that gets results from agriculture. For example, fruit and vegetable farmers are planted in rice fields, fields, to mountainous areas.</string>
    <string name="desc3">Doctors include jobs that produce services. Doctors work and serve the interests of humanity. Doctors work to prevent, examine and treat sick patients.</string>
    <string name="desc4">Employees usually work in companies or government offices. They are needed for personnel and abilities according to their field of expertise.</string>
    <string name="desc5">Teachers are tasked with educating and teaching knowledge to students.</string>
    <string name="desc6">People who work in libraries include the type of work that produces services. The librarian is responsible for managing and providing services in the library.</string>
    <string name="desc7">Fisherman work to find fish in the sea. So, most of the fisherman live in areas near the coast. These catches will be resold to the market. Usually fishermen sell fish that are still fresh taken in the sea.</string>
    <string name="desc8">People who have the expertise to make clothes are called tailors. This job requires skills to cut fabrics, make patterns, and turn fabrics into clothes.</string>
    <string name="desc9">People breed livestock for resale. Examples of livestock are goats, cows, chickens, rabbits, cows, and ducks. The farm animals are treated to produce meat, eggs, milk, or skins which are sold in the market.</string>
    <string name="desc10">Soldiers are tasked with maintaining national security in the field of defense.</string>
</resources>